This love in my heart,
it will burn on forever.
Granting me courage, I
hope it will never stop.
No matter where you
are, nothing is too far.
With our everlasting bones,
we'll reach it, we are home.
I'm
so truly grateful.
I ran into you on that day so long ago.
We laughed every moment
with tears in our eyes.
Till we knew we weren't alone.
The blowing wind came in
and joined us on our way.
And with it I know we'll rise.
We'll be flying up high.
Why, tell me why are you giving up?
Why, tell me why you want to fight alone?
Hey, what kind of future
do you think you have?
Your dream is already in your hands.
This love in my heart,
it will burn off forever!
Granting me courage, I
hope it will never stop.
I don't matter where you
are, nothing is too far.
With our everlasting
problems, we'll reach it.
We are home from the horizon,
out on the edge of the world.
If there is a place that
I want to take you to?
Let's head forward then.
But as for the way we already know,
We promised it long ago.
You scream by your voice.
That can't break through the silence.
Feeling defeated?
It crushes your helpless heart.
I've got your back, I swear.
I'll always be here.
Let's put our fate within
this light under the sun.
Can you close your eyes and
just listen to my voice?
Let's find the answer together I'm
telling you in our path I trust that it
will lead us To another sea untarded
Cause now we are home On the horizon,
out on the edge of the world
There is a place that I want to take you
to Let's head for it
then But after the way,
we already know
We promised it long ago
They're gonna duel!
Huh?
Who's going to?
Lord Judge has taken on
that pirate Sanji Sanji?
And I heard he already beat up Master
Yoji What kind of monster is he?
That lout was still refusing the marriage,
so I tried to step in on Father's behalf.
Just like old times.
And then this happens!
He'll pay for this!
He's such an arrogant asshole!
It appears we'll need to use a tool
more powerful than the hammer, sir.
Starting to press.
Hold still a second. Huh?
And I believe that does it.
Screw that guy.
He's a reject, a
disappointment, and a failure.
That's Master Sanji.
I trust you're prepared.
Anytime you're ready.
Very well.
Time to duel!
They're both so quick.
It's no surprise.
Master Sanji had a hefty
bounty on his head after all.
It's not a shame to kick your father, huh?
Guess the guy who started
this in the first place.
And stop saying you're my father.
It's getting on my nerves.
Like it or not, you are my son, Saji.
So why are you trying to stab me then?
He's powerful.
And he's fighting
without a raid suit, too.
Once the tea party ends, I'm
booking it back to my ship.
I won't really marry her.
Still spouting off.
This is all about strengthening your forces
by forming a bond with Big Mom, right?
So it shouldn't matter
where I go afterwards.
The issue is not that simple.
You'd stain the Vinsmoke name.
Big Mom would punish such treasury.
You'd be mistaken if you think I give
a crap what happens to you chumps.
Besides, I only came here
to save my friends' lives.
You depended your family?
You bastards were never my family!
Yep, he was in the kitchen.
Sanji was making some
of that rat food again.
Royalty doesn't cook.
You shut up!
Give it back!
Ouch.
You piece of trash!
Don't ever touch me again!
Oh, it is so weak!
You were all bored all the same day!
How are we related to such a loser?
You're a failure.
Father's here.
Picking on Sanji again?
They hurt me, Father.
Can you tell them to stop?
Why should I?
Father...
If you are not a fighter and you
are unable to stand up for yourself,
I have no obligation to help you.
I gain nothing by raising you.
Why would you say that?
You're a disgrace to the family name.
On your feet, I'll toughen you up!
You're such a disgrace?
All right, Yonji have at him.
This is gonna be fun
Ha!
Reminiscing on old times, are you?
He blocked the blade with his leg.
The evil son I once knew
we'll talk, you know?
Fetch a sword. Huh? Sir!
Take it.
What's the matter?
Surely you haven't forgotten my teachings.
If you knew me at all, you'd
realize I never use that crap.
Get this through your skull.
My hands are for cooking only.
Wow, weak little Sanji's
become quite strong.
For cooking, you say?
That's absurd.
Are you still making rat food?
Serving is not a talent befit for royalty.
It's ludicrous.
You're out of touch, old man.
Why resist the marriage?
Don't you know what's good for you?
He's still in close combat mode.
So this is how the
legendary Carrot fights.
You don't get to see this every day.
An aerial attack?
How ironic.
That's my forte.
Diablo-jamba.
Gol-yay. Go!
Go!
War is the catalyst for
scientific progress!
Electromagnetic crux!
Blaster!
The Germa you were once familiar
with is now a relic of the past.
Little Sanji, I got
something I want to ask.
Do you owe someone respect just
because you're elated by blood?
What do you say?
Any fond memories of him?
Can't think of one, can you?
I'm sorry.
Father, let me out!
You suffered so much.
It's so dark in here!
Please, Father!
Boil up, Freer!
I'm sure you've got nothing
but anger towards him.
Wall up!
Look out!
He's heading straight for you!
E .M.
Chef, go!
I'm surprised.
You're tough as nails.
I still can't believe
you're the same Sanji.
You are so helpless.
You can save the small talk.
After this damn tea party's over, I'm out.
Then I'll be free from Big
Mom's invitation curse.
I was hoping you'd be less of a scumbag,
but it seems you've only gotten worse.
Get out of this room, geezer.
You're stranger to me.
No chance.
Need I remind you that's
my blood in your veins?
Do not be mistaken.
What you witnessed today, boy?,
was an example of how loyal
the Germa soldiers truly are?
willing to give their
lives at a moment's notice.
Their unwavering devotion is
the backbone of Jerma's power.
Then why the hell aren't you using them
to chase your stupid, grandiose dreams?
You wanted to conquer
the North Blue, right?
Terrific.
That's perfect for an evil army.
Precisely.
You're quick on the uptake.
By forming an alliance with Big Mom,
it will strengthen our forces tenfold.
And that dream can soon become a reality.
If you can comprehend at least
that much, I'm satisfied.
Honestly, I did not intend to
ruffle any feathers, Sanji.
I require Big Mom's help,
but unfortunately she demands
a blood connection in return.
Frankly,
I do not relish the thought
of marrying off one of my
invaluable sons to someone in
that demented madwoman's lineage.
Then I remembered, years
ago, I had another child.
Who was an absolute failure?
You'll be a sacrifice for
the family, understood?
I haven't changed my opinion of you, and
I do not think of you as a worthy son.
Just so we're clear.
Huh?
What's this about?
You mentioned your hands
are important to you.
That works in my favor.
You know of the collars the Celestial
Dragons put on their slaves, yes?
If they try to escape from their masters,
it detonates, removing their heads.
These are rigged to work the same way.
If you try to flee, your
hands will be blown off.
Huh? Screw you! Take them off!
Fortunately, Big Mom had the
foresight to lend those to me.
She's the only one who possesses the key.
Are you serious?
Stop that.
I wouldn't fuss with them if I were you.
Using the key is the only
way to take them off.
Safely, that is.
You can't run away.
Cuffs or no cuffs.
Because I have the entire German
army to put you in your place.
We will see this marriage through.
Extra!
Soto Land News!
I can't believe Boss
Jinbei betrayed Big Mom.
It says it all happened yesterday.
Things move fast.
That's a crying shame.
The way he marched on up and stopped
Mama's food tantrum was pretty damn cool.
Well, as I understand it,
he has to leave her crew.
You better believe he took that back in
a second soon as he heard the price wait.
Are you for real?
Wow, that's pathetic
I guess being the first son of the sea
means nothing to that traitor, man.
I lost respect for that coward.
What a loser
I
was unaware you were working
for big mom that must
be why fish man island
was under her protection?
So this Jinbei fellow, he was
a former warlord, that correct?
How's someone like him her subordinate?
Tell me, Brook, do you
Karoo know this man? We do.
He's a rather important person to us.
And if you haven't changed
your mind and still
wish for me to become
a member of your crew,
well, I'll gladly take you up on your
offer then, if you see fit to have me.
I suppose this is what he
meant by having obligations.
I wonder what kind of business he
could have with Big Mom, though.
This article still befuddles me.
It doesn't sound like the Jinbei we know.
Is he preparing to come see us?
Hey, Brooke!
Can we hurry?
I have somewhere I need to go.
Mademoiselle Pudding, whatever
your matter of urgency is,
it can wait, n 'est-ce pas?
Nothing could be more important
than choosing the correct author!
I'll be late.
Lady Pudding!
What's your opinion on this?
I think it would suit you well.
How about this one? I knew it.
That color will look wonderful on you.
You could honestly wear any of these.
I'm jealous.
Do any of these jump out
at you, Lady Pudding?
Well, do you perhaps know which
one the groom would prefer then?
I wouldn't know.
I've only met him once, you see.
What?
Hold on just a minute.
Shouldn't she be meeting
with Luffy right now?
It appears that she can't break away
from her hand servants at the moment.
Oh dear,
I hope the others aren't in trouble now
that the plan has gone horribly awry!
If this is how it's gone,
that probably means that Sanji
doesn't even realize we're here.
Who did Luffy see back at the shore then?
Who do I say?
Not a clue, but we can assume he
mistook someone else for Sanji
It's that egg guy!
I believe I've seen him
on Big Mom's ship before.
Yeah, I know him all too well.
His name's Baron Tamago.
Baron Tamago, may I speak with you?
Oi, what is it?
It's about the Straw Hat ship that
landed at Chocolatown yesterday.
THEY ALREADY KNOW!
It's really rather unfortunate.
It seems after they left, Mr.
Peckham's, who escorted the pirates
here, was nowhere to be found, sir.
THEY KNOW EVERYTHING!
However, as for the four Straw Hats who
wandered into the seducing woods today...
They're already cornered!
They're as good as captured!
THEY'RE ALREADY CAUGHT!
But the whereabouts of
the other two are unknown.
This is them.
That's us!
How do they have so much dirt?
They know every intimate detail.
They had to have been
spying on us somehow.
That is l 'erreur, it declares
that le mink is a panther.
He's en Fight a jaguar.
It s 'appelle Pedro.
Oh, do you know him?
I shall just say, we have a past.
As for Mr.
Minx's next step, I believe I
have an idea of what is up to.
Ce ne Fight Rain.
Your order is to seek
out Pec-Holmes! Yes, sir!
Poor Pec-Holmes, mon ami.
Since you were surprisingly still alive,
I had hoped to ask Mama to pardon you.
But your involvement with les parades
makes that très compliqué for moi.
You are quite the handful, c 'est la vie.
Oh, man!
We are in big trouble!
Hey, shut your trap, Junior.
Be a good baby and suck it up!
Oh, you got him laughing!
Nice job, Papa!
There we go.
Who's my big shot? You are.
What a good little goon you are.
Aw, Junior.
I hope you'll become a big, strong,
wise guy, just like your pops one day.
I can't stand this sappy crap. Get out!
Yeah, the real looker, ain't he?
You know what's funny?
His life is just beginning,
and yours is coming to a close.
It's like one of them
high-concept artsy paintings.
Don't you agree?
You know, you got no one to
blame but yourself, Peckums.
You chose this fate.
Remember, I gave you a chance.
It didn't seem too charitable
if you ask me. Get out!
Need I remind you what
happened back in Zo?
They won't get your crap in this world.
Sorry to break it to you, pal, but you
ain't cut out for this line of work.
You know why I brought you here, old boy?
It's the perfect place to lose a body.
Got any last words?
You don't know what you're
getting into with mama!
Now, let me see.
see your hands.
They're covered in bruises.
Stupid brat.
What's your deal, you old geezer?
I've explained this before.
Don't you ever use your
hands for fighting.
Dammit!
Ah, now I believe that I have
given you more than ample funding.
Wouldn't you agree with me, Caesar?
Yes, of course, ma 'am.
I continued the research
the entire time, too.
My dream's almost reality.
This pleases me so.
I wish for all races around the
world to become one big family.
And sit around the table at the
same eye level with one another.
I want them all to
partake in what I drink.
And indulge whatever I devour.
Doesn't a world like that sound divine to
you and that dream will soon come true?
All thanks to you, Caesar, dear.
I want you to make my family
grow to the size of giants.
With the power of science, your research
must be close to finished by now.
You kept saying the
project was complete, but you needed a
little extra money to keep research going.
I hope all that cash I
funneled your way helped you.
I'm quite eager to know how things went.
Well, uh,
swimmingly thanks to your generosity.
The gigantification of the human body.
Yes, I was doing the experiments.
The whole world wants to get
their hands on that technology.
However my testing was only
done on children and the
results were rather grim
frankly i was Confident that
the whole endeavor was
fruitless from the start you
can't turn ordinary people
Giant with some magic drug like
she asked that's why i
cheated her out of as much
money as she Could bleed i
splurged every last berry on
seafaring call girls she doesn't
even realize The research
she was paying for funded
my booze and women binges.
Those were the good old days.
I could hide behind Joker and
get away with whatever I wanted.
Who could have guessed he
would ever be defeated, though?
My fast and loose lifestyle has
finally caught up with me. Damn it!
And here I thought I'd be
untouchable for the rest of my life?
This is all because of
that miserable pirate!
What's with those faces, Caesar?
Well, you see, that's right about us.
Everything, and I mean
everything, fell through on me.
That damn Straw Hat Luffy took advantage
of the tireless work I was doing for you.
And just as my research was
approaching the finish line.
He and that dumb Trafalgar
Law came and screwed it up.
If it weren't for those two brats, the
gigantism drug would have been completed.
It was just within my grasp.
I'm sad to report that
the special lab built by
the world government was
total thanks to them.
And I could only achieve results in a
perfectly controlled
environment like that one.
The money you invested in that lab
containing my hard work it's all gone.
I can no longer create
the gigantism drug because
those damn pirates
ruined everything for us!
A tragedy my hard work destroyed.
Do you need another lab
like on Punk Castle?
I have one just like it.
I acquired the blueprint to it ages ago.
Our minister of candy is quite skilled
and can make anything out of sweets,
you know.
Tell me what you need and you'll have
unlimited funds at your disposal. What?
Are you being serious right now, ma 'am?
I mean, I appreciate it. So?
So?
When will it be ready? Huh?
Oh.
One week?
Two weeks?
I can't wait.
This is ridiculous.
Mankind has been at this for
centuries with no results.
How will I talk my way out of this one?
Huh?
Lickety-lick, lickety-lick.
Does the laboratory meet
your standard, Caesar?
It's a spitting image of
your old one, is it not?
Coo-coo-coo-coo.
Plus, the interior has
the same lickety-layout.
Coo-coo-coo-coo.
Huh?
That's mine.
No, don't touch it!
Now that ticker can take a licking.
Curse you!
Wait a second, don't leave yet, Blackleg.
Give me back my heart before
you head out. Oh, yeah.
Here.
You got two weeks, so you had better
produce the gigantism drug Lickety Split.
If it takes any longer than that,
I'll turn you into a candy man
and lick you down to nothing.
In just two weeks I'll be dead.
I have to figure something out.
It's you again?
That's like 12 times now.
Welcome back.
I found more.
You've gathered up so many of them.
Choke! Choke!
I don't understand, guys.
Choke! Choke! Choke!
How are you multiplying? Tell me!